{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Pool Enclosure Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40371/":{"taskOID":40371,"originalTaskOID":40371,"setID":665,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":269,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5130,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Remodel to existing structure","answerDisplayText":"Remodel to existing structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4132,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"New Construction","answerDisplayText":"New Construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":675,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Addition","answerDisplayText":"Addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":272,"questionDisplayText":"Roof Options","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Choose your roofing options.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4514,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Overhead glass","answerDisplayText":"Overhead glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4584,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Partial overhead glass","answerDisplayText":"Partial overhead glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5416,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Roofing (no overhead glass)","answerDisplayText":"Roofing (no overhead glass)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":273,"questionDisplayText":"Options","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select from the following options. (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3429,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Knee walls","answerDisplayText":"Knee walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4430,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Operable windows","answerDisplayText":"Operable windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5795,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sliding glass door","answerDisplayText":"Sliding glass door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4498,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Outside shade screens","answerDisplayText":"Outside shade screens","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3786,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Mechanical exhaust fan","answerDisplayText":"Mechanical exhaust fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6991,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Window glazing","answerDisplayText":"Window glazing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5504,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Screened walls","answerDisplayText":"Screened walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2649,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"French door(s)","answerDisplayText":"French door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7002,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Window tinting","answerDisplayText":"Window tinting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":269,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5130,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Remodel to existing structure","answerDisplayText":"Remodel to existing structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4132,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"New Construction","answerDisplayText":"New Construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":675,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Addition","answerDisplayText":"Addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5130,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Remodel to existing structure","answerDisplayText":"Remodel to existing structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4132,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"New Construction","answerDisplayText":"New Construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":675,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Addition","answerDisplayText":"Addition","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":272,"questionDisplayText":"Roof Options","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Choose your roofing options.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4514,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Overhead glass","answerDisplayText":"Overhead glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4584,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Partial overhead glass","answerDisplayText":"Partial overhead glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5416,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Roofing (no overhead glass)","answerDisplayText":"Roofing (no overhead glass)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4514,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Overhead glass","answerDisplayText":"Overhead glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4584,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Partial overhead glass","answerDisplayText":"Partial overhead glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5416,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Roofing (no overhead glass)","answerDisplayText":"Roofing (no overhead glass)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":273,"questionDisplayText":"Options","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select from the following options. (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3429,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Knee walls","answerDisplayText":"Knee walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4430,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Operable windows","answerDisplayText":"Operable windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5795,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sliding glass door","answerDisplayText":"Sliding glass door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4498,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Outside shade screens","answerDisplayText":"Outside shade screens","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3786,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Mechanical exhaust fan","answerDisplayText":"Mechanical exhaust fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6991,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Window glazing","answerDisplayText":"Window glazing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5504,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Screened walls","answerDisplayText":"Screened walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2649,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"French door(s)","answerDisplayText":"French door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7002,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Window tinting","answerDisplayText":"Window tinting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3429,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Knee walls","answerDisplayText":"Knee walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4430,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Operable windows","answerDisplayText":"Operable windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5795,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Sliding glass door","answerDisplayText":"Sliding glass door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4498,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Outside shade screens","answerDisplayText":"Outside shade screens","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3786,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Mechanical exhaust fan","answerDisplayText":"Mechanical exhaust fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6991,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Window glazing","answerDisplayText":"Window glazing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5504,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Screened walls","answerDisplayText":"Screened walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2649,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"French door(s)","answerDisplayText":"French door(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7002,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Window tinting","answerDisplayText":"Window tinting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40371/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40371,"taskName":"Pool Enclosure - Build","taskDescription":"Build a Pool Enclosure","xmTaskDescriptor":"Pool Enclosure Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":185,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Pool Build freestanding building hot","textMessagingName":"Inst Pool Encl","rolloverLongDesc":"These systems can have steel, aluminum or wood frames \u0026 either glass or plastic skins. Looking somewhat like a greenhouse, they seal off the pool area from the elements eliminating problems with debris \u0026 bugs \u0026 allowing for continued use on colder seasons.","rolloverShortDesc":"Roof structure protects pool \u0026 extends season.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Build a Pool Enclosure.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Pool Enclosure Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Build Swimming Pool Enclosure","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":37,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Pool Enclosure Build","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Pool Enclosure - Build","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Pool Enclosure Project","urlName":"Pool-Enclosure-Build","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Pool Enclosure Builders \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"Pool,Build,freestanding,building,hot,patio,addition,steel,free,swimming,tub,outbuilding,out,Enclosure","emcCategoryOid":-12063,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":665,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}